
let quiz = [{
  question: "How many timezones are there in the world?",
  option: ["12","16","24","10"],
  answer:2
}, {
  question: "What is the time difference between Pacific time and Eastern time?",
  option:["Pacific time is 3 hours later","Pacific time is two hours earlier","Pacific time is 3 hours earlier", "Pacific time is 2 hours later"],
  answer:0
  },{
  question: "!Which of these countries has the highest per capita CO2 emissions?",
  option:[ "USA","China","India","UK"],
  answer:1
},{
  question:"what does the abbreviation EST stand for?",
  option:["East, South Time","Eastern Southern Time","Eastern Standard Time","It doesn't stand anything"],
  answer:2
},
{
  question:"How many timezones are there in the Finland?",
  option:["3", "2", "5", "1"],
  answer:3
},{
  question:"The total set of carbon emissions caused by an individual.",
  option: ["carbon Cycle", "Carbon footprint", "Carbon handprint", "Carbon summary"],
  answer: 1
},{
  question: "What is the most potent greenhouse gas?",
  option: ["Fluorinated gases"," Carbon dioxide"," Nitrous gas","Methane"],
  answer: 0
},{
  question: "The main human activity adds to an individual's carbon footprint.",
  option:["usage of alternatives energies.","Respiration and growth","Photosynthesis by plants","Usage of fossils fuel for energy"],
  answer:1
},{
  question:"Which of these choices in transportation produces less greenhouse gas than the others?",
  option:["Riding a bus","Walking","Taking a train","Riding a car"],
  answer:1
},{
  question: "Which one is not the fossils fuel?",
  option:["coal", "Natural gas","oil","wood"],
  answer:3
}

]
